<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tommaso Sorrentino</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/LobsterRavioli/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tommaso Sorrentino</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:48:10 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/LobsterRavioli/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Start my cloud career</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/LobsterRavioli/posts/cloud_computing_career/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:48:10 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/LobsterRavioli/posts/cloud_computing_career/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s rapidly evolving tech landscape, cloud computing has emerged as a cornerstone of modern IT infrastructure. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned IT professional looking to expand your skill set or a newcomer to the tech world, embarking on a cloud career can open up a world of opportunities.&#xA;Why Cloud Computing? Cloud computing offers several advantages:&#xA;Scalability: Easily scale resources up or down based on demand. Cost Efficiency: Pay only for the resources you use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/LobsterRavioli/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 10:49:16 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/LobsterRavioli/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>This is my first post using Hugo, a powerful static site generator. In this post, I&amp;rsquo;ll share my experience setting up my blog and a few tips for getting started with Hugo.&#xA;Getting Started with Hugo Hugo is a fast and flexible static site generator written in Go. It&amp;rsquo;s designed for speed and ease of use, making it a popular choice for creating blogs and websites. Here&amp;rsquo;s how I set up my blog:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/LobsterRavioli/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/LobsterRavioli/about/</guid>
      <description>👋 Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Tommaso Sorrentino, a recent graduate with a degree in Computer Science from University of Salerno. 🎓 I am enthusiastic about diving into the world of cloud computing and leveraging technology to solve real-world problems.&#xA;💻 Throughout my academic journey, I have developed strong skills in programming languages such as JavaScript, Python, and Java. I have a keen interest in cloud technologies and have been actively learning about platforms like AWS, Azure, and Google Cloud.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
